[{"id":"bbb966f0-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"exemplify","ans":[{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":true},{"value":"a situation or period of time when there is a new interest in something that has not been popular in a long time; A period of new growth or activity","isTrue":false},{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":false},{"value":"different from what you would expect : not agreeing with what seems right or natural","isTrue":false}],"examples":["His works exemplify the taste of the period.","The city's economic growth is exemplified by the many new buildings that are currently under construction."]},{"id":"bbbb89d0-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"stoop","ans":[{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false},{"value":"lower one's moral standards so far as to do something reprehensible.","isTrue":true},{"value":"a state of extreme happiness, especially when feeling pleasure:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Don't stoop so low for money."]},{"id":"bbbb89d1-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"quorum","ans":[{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make a very serious or emotional request to (someone);to ask or beg for (something) in a very serious or emotional way","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false},{"value":"the smallest number of people needed to be present at a meeting before it can officially begin and before official decisions can be taken.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["We can start our meeting as we have quorum now."]},{"id":"bbbb89d2-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"quid pro quo","ans":[{"value":"a quality that makes one person or thing different from another","isTrue":false},{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":false},{"value":"able to be understood:","isTrue":false},{"value":"Something that is given to a person in return for something they have done, often use in a bad sense.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Judges often get quid pro quo from government for favourable their verdicts."]},{"id":"bbbb89d3-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"prudent","ans":[{"value":"Something that is given to a person in return for something they have done, often use in a bad sense.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the act of using someone unfairly for your own advantage","isTrue":false},{"value":"to cause an angry, harmful, or violent action or feeling","isTrue":false},{"value":"careful and avoiding risks:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["It's always prudent to read a contract carefully before signing it."]},{"id":"bbbb89d4-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"renaissance","ans":[{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":false},{"value":"a situation or period of time when there is a new interest in something that has not been popular in a long time; A period of new growth or activity","isTrue":true},{"value":"very strongly felt; very great; absolute or complete","isTrue":false},{"value":"to form an opinion or to make an estimate about something from known facts","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The JavaScript renaissance is upon us."]},{"id":"bbbb89d5-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"idiosyncrasy (idio-syn-crasy)","ans":[{"value":"not aware of or not noticing something, esp. what is happening around you","isTrue":false},{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a strange or unusual habit, way of behaving, or feature that someone or something has:","isTrue":true},{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":false}],"examples":["One of her many idiosyncrasies is always smelling a book before opening it","web is littered with examples of each browser's idiosyncrasies"]},{"id":"bbbb89d6-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"albeit (Al-be-it)","ans":[{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":false},{"value":"despite the stated thing; although:","isTrue":true},{"value":"the suffering and death of a martyr.","isTrue":false},{"value":"Something that is given to a person in return for something they have done, often use in a bad sense.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The nation is adapting, albeit slowly, to the new global economy.","The evening was very pleasant, albeit a little quiet."]},{"id":"bbbb89d7-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"confidant","ans":[{"value":"causing a feeling of great surprise or wonder : causing astonishment","isTrue":false},{"value":"a phrase or statement that seems to say two opposite things, like \"agree to disagree\"","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":true},{"value":"not clear in meaning; not thinking or expressing your thoughts clearly or precisely;","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He is a close confidant of King."]},{"id":"bbbb89d8-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"incommunicado","ans":[{"value":"a situation or period of time when there is a new interest in something that has not been popular in a long time; A period of new growth or activity","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":false},{"value":"not communicating with anyone else because you do not want to or are not allowed to:","isTrue":true},{"value":"unhappy, disappointed, or without hope","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He is in incommunicado after he lost the match.","He was held incommunicado for the first 48 hours after he was arrested."]},{"id":"bbbb89d9-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"moratorium","ans":[{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false},{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":true},{"value":"to agree with someone or something","isTrue":false},{"value":"angry and bitter (typically of speech or discussion)","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The RBI has imposed a moratorium on YES Bank."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e0-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"utopian","ans":[{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"relating to or aiming for a perfect society in which everyone works well with each other and is happy:","isTrue":true},{"value":"a person who is killed or who suffers greatly for a religion, cause, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["a utopian vision."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e1-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"contemplate/contemplating","ans":[{"value":"the advocacy of women's rights on the ground of the equality of the sexes.","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":false},{"value":"To look at on all sides or in all its aspects; To consider as a possibility.","isTrue":true},{"value":"to cause an angry, harmful, or violent action or feeling","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I'm contemplating leaving my job."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e2-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"hullabaloo","ans":[{"value":"seeming impossible or difficult to understand because of containing two opposite facts or characteristics","isTrue":false},{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":false},{"value":"trouble or annoyance; deep sadness caused especially by someone's death;","isTrue":false},{"value":"a loud noise made by people who are angry or annoyed; a lot of angry comments made in public about someone or something:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["There's a crowd of angry demonstrators making a real hullabaloo outside the Houses of Parliament."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e3-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"constellation","ans":[{"value":"a group of famous or admired people all together in one place;any of the groups of stars in the sky that seem from earth to form a pattern and have been given names","isTrue":true},{"value":"the way in which you express your feelings, thoughts and ideas, etc., in words","isTrue":false},{"value":"said or done in a forceful or definite way; resounding","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of being completely forgotten or destroyed.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["At our annual ceremony we had a whole constellation of movie stars and directors."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e4-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"narcissistic","ans":[{"value":"not clear in meaning; not thinking or expressing your thoughts clearly or precisely;","isTrue":false},{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":true},{"value":"easily broken, torn, etc. : not strong or solid","isTrue":false},{"value":"a state of extreme happiness, especially when feeling pleasure:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I found her to be self-absorbed and narcissistic."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e5-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"outlier","ans":[{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person, thing, or fact that is very different from other people, things, or facts, so that it cannot be used to draw general conclusions","isTrue":true},{"value":"to make something less clear and harder to understand, especially intentionally","isTrue":false},{"value":"no longer living; A person who has recently died, days or years","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The poll that showed him increasing support by 5 points was probably an outlier."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e6-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"oxymoron","ans":[{"value":"a phrase or statement that seems to say two opposite things, like \"agree to disagree\"","isTrue":true},{"value":"to form an opinion or to make an estimate about something from known facts","isTrue":false},{"value":"without wasting more time;","isTrue":false},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["My room is an organized mess.","Act naturally","Agree to disagree.","He lived for the cause, by dying for it. What a Oxymoron."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e7-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"dejected","ans":[{"value":"a short line with many curves : a short, wavy line.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"unhappy, disappointed, or without hope","isTrue":true},{"value":"not truly honest or sincere : giving the false appearance of being honest or sincere","isTrue":false}],"examples":["She looked a bit dejected when they told her she didn't get the job"]},{"id":"bbbbb0e8-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"acrimonious","ans":[{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":false},{"value":"not communicating with anyone else because you do not want to or are not allowed to:","isTrue":false},{"value":"angry and bitter (typically of speech or discussion)","isTrue":true},{"value":"a comparison of two things based on their being alike in some way","isTrue":false}],"examples":["an acrimonious debate","acrimonious disputes between nations","He went through an acrimonious divorce."]},{"id":"bbbbb0e9-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"counter-intuitive","ans":[{"value":"different from what you would expect : not agreeing with what seems right or natural","isTrue":true},{"value":"a very slight difference in appearance, meaning, sound, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"When a word or sentence used with a meaning that is different from it's literal meaning; \"tons of work\" or \"\"","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person, thing, or fact that is very different from other people, things, or facts, so that it cannot be used to draw general conclusions","isTrue":false}],"examples":["It may seem counterintuitive, but we do burn calories when we are sleeping"]},{"id":"bbbbb0ea-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"bliss","ans":[{"value":"perfect happiness","isTrue":true},{"value":"said or done in a forceful or definite way; resounding","isTrue":false},{"value":"To look at on all sides or in all its aspects; To consider as a possibility.","isTrue":false},{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Lying on a sunny beach is my idea of sheer bliss."]},{"id":"bbbbb0eb-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"affluence","ans":[{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":false},{"value":"unusual and strange, sometimes in an unpleasant way","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":true},{"value":"a strange or unusual habit, way of behaving, or feature that someone or something has:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["This period saw the increase of real wages and affluence in British society."]},{"id":"bbbbb0ec-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"enumerate","ans":[{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":false},{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He enumerated the benefits of the insurance scheme.","The salesman enumerated the features of the car."]},{"id":"bbbbb0ed-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"grif","ans":[{"value":"without wasting more time;","isTrue":false},{"value":"a situation or period of time when there is a new interest in something that has not been popular in a long time; A period of new growth or activity","isTrue":false},{"value":"the smallest number of people needed to be present at a meeting before it can officially begin and before official decisions can be taken.","isTrue":false},{"value":"trouble or annoyance; deep sadness caused especially by someone's death;","isTrue":true}],"examples":["In our experience, changes in law bring more grief than benefit.","He has been unable to recover from his grief at/over his son's death."]},{"id":"bbbbb0ee-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"comprehensible","ans":[{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false},{"value":"a short line with many curves : a short, wavy line.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":false},{"value":"able to be understood:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["It's written in clear, comprehensible English.","Her writing is barely comprehensible to me."]},{"id":"bbbbb0ef-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"God forbid","ans":[{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false},{"value":"a way of saying that you hope something does not happen:","isTrue":true},{"value":"a very slight difference in appearance, meaning, sound, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to agree with someone or something","isTrue":false}],"examples":["If God forbid, World war 3 happen, who will save the world."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f0-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"procrastination","ans":[{"value":"trouble or annoyance; deep sadness caused especially by someone's death;","isTrue":false},{"value":"done before someone else can do it","isTrue":false},{"value":"to support, strengthen, or defend (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"to be slow or late about doing something that should be done; to delay doing something until a later time because you do not want to do it, because you are lazy, etc.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He procrastinated and missed the submission deadline.","Some people are procrastinators when it comes to paying their bills."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f1-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"conglomerate (/kənˈɡlɒm.ər.ət/)","ans":[{"value":"to drink quickly, eagerly, and usually in large amounts","isTrue":false},{"value":"a strange or unusual habit, way of behaving, or feature that someone or something has:","isTrue":false},{"value":"To look at on all sides or in all its aspects; To consider as a possibility.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a company that owns several smaller businesses whose products or services are usually very different:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Tata is a conglomerate"]},{"id":"bbbbb0f2-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"scant","ans":[{"value":"a very slight difference in appearance, meaning, sound, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to agree with someone or something","isTrue":false},{"value":"very little and not enough:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Food was in scant supply.","She paid scant attention to the facts."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f3-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"ecstasy (/ˈek.stə.si/ )","ans":[{"value":"a situation in which many people behave or react in an extreme or uncontrolled way because of fear, anger, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false},{"value":"the way in which you express your feelings, thoughts and ideas, etc., in words","isTrue":false},{"value":"a state of extreme happiness, especially when feeling pleasure:","isTrue":true}],"examples":["We shared a moment of ecstasy as the chocolate melted on our tongues."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f4-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"paradoxical","ans":[{"value":"seeming impossible or difficult to understand because of containing two opposite facts or characteristics","isTrue":true},{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":false},{"value":"trouble or annoyance; deep sadness caused especially by someone's death;","isTrue":false},{"value":"not communicating with anyone else because you do not want to or are not allowed to:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["It seems paradoxical to me, but if you drink a cup of hot tea it seems to cool you down.","Sometime to do more you have to do less. Such a Paradox!"]},{"id":"bbbbb0f5-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"chutzpah (/ˈhʊtspə/ )","ans":[{"value":"the smallest number of people needed to be present at a meeting before it can officially begin and before official decisions can be taken.","isTrue":false},{"value":"individually separate and distinct.","isTrue":false},{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":true},{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false}],"examples":["It took a lot of chutzpah [=nerve] to stand up to him the way she did.","The movie was made with a little money and a lot of chutzpah"]},{"id":"bbbbb0f6-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"vitiated","ans":[{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":true},{"value":"a way of saying that you hope something does not happen:","isTrue":false},{"value":"Something that is given to a person in return for something they have done, often use in a bad sense.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The impact of the film was vitiated by poor acting.","Once a top institute, it is vitiated over time."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f7-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"lofty","ans":[{"value":"a way of saying that you hope something does not happen:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to keep doing something even though it is difficult or boring","isTrue":false},{"value":"very strongly felt; very great; absolute or complete","isTrue":false},{"value":"very high; with great height","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Politicians very often make very lofty promises, which they fail to deliver."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f8-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"articulation","ans":[{"value":"the state of being completely forgotten or destroyed.","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":false},{"value":"the way in which you express your feelings, thoughts and ideas, etc., in words","isTrue":true},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The book is the articulation of his vision.","They way he articulated his vision, that was just brilliant."]},{"id":"bbbbb0f9-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"inane","ans":[{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":false},{"value":"not communicating with anyone else because you do not want to or are not allowed to:","isTrue":false},{"value":"extremely silly or with no real meaning or importance","isTrue":true},{"value":"a state of extreme happiness, especially when feeling pleasure:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He's always making inane remarks.","He grinned inanely."]},{"id":"bbbbb0fa-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"discrete","ans":[{"value":"careful and avoiding risks:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":false},{"value":"to want to be able to move away from something because you fear it","isTrue":false},{"value":"individually separate and distinct.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["speech sounds are produced as a continuous sound signal rather than discrete units"]},{"id":"bbbbd7f0-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"realm","ans":[{"value":"an area of interest or activity","isTrue":true},{"value":"to make something less clear and harder to understand, especially intentionally","isTrue":false},{"value":"perfect happiness","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Her interests are in the realm of practical politics.","It's my realm."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f1-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"oblivious","ans":[{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"not aware of or not noticing something, esp. what is happening around you","isTrue":true},{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false},{"value":"a very slight difference in appearance, meaning, sound, etc.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Absorbed in her work, she was totally oblivious of her surroundings."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f2-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"oblivion","ans":[{"value":"different from what you would expect : not agreeing with what seems right or natural","isTrue":false},{"value":"trouble or annoyance; deep sadness caused especially by someone's death;","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of being completely forgotten or destroyed.","isTrue":true},{"value":"not aware of or not noticing something, esp. what is happening around you","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Her work was rescued from oblivion when it was rediscovered in the early 1900s."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f3-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"concur","ans":[{"value":"to agree or have the same opinion","isTrue":true},{"value":"to keep doing something even though it is difficult or boring","isTrue":false},{"value":"unusual and strange, sometimes in an unpleasant way","isTrue":false},{"value":"a group of famous or admired people all together in one place;any of the groups of stars in the sky that seem from earth to form a pattern and have been given names","isTrue":false}],"examples":["We concur that more money should be spent on education."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f4-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"succinct","ans":[{"value":"the smallest number of people needed to be present at a meeting before it can officially begin and before official decisions can be taken.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a comparison of two things based on their being alike in some way","isTrue":false},{"value":"to agree or have the same opinion","isTrue":false},{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Keep your letter succinct and to the point."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f5-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"quail","ans":[{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"an area of interest or activity","isTrue":false},{"value":"to want to be able to move away from something because you fear it","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Charlie quailed at the sound of his mother's angry voice.","She quailed before her boss's anger."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f6-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"figurative","ans":[{"value":"a situation in which many people behave or react in an extreme or uncontrolled way because of fear, anger, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"When a word or sentence used with a meaning that is different from it's literal meaning; \"tons of work\" or \"\"","isTrue":true},{"value":"very harsh and critical","isTrue":false},{"value":"unhappy, disappointed, or without hope","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I hear you've got a new job (not literally, but figurative).","I have tons of work (not literally, but figurative)."],"info":"When speech or writing is not literal, it is figurative, like when you say you have a ton of homework. You don't really have 2000 pounds of homework, do you?Also, The phrase “know your ropes” means literally “to know a lot about ropes,” while its figurative meaning is “to know a lot about how to do something.”"},{"id":"bbbbd7f7-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"foresee","ans":[{"value":"to make (someone) do something by using force or threats","isTrue":false},{"value":"a phrase or statement that seems to say two opposite things, like \"agree to disagree\"","isTrue":false},{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":true},{"value":"despite the stated thing; although:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I don't foresee any difficulties so long as we keep within budget."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f8-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"pretentious","ans":[{"value":"trying to appear or sound more important or clever than you are, especially in matters of art and literature","isTrue":true},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"perfect happiness","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["a pretentious art critic.","I always found him pretentious, when he speak."]},{"id":"bbbbd7f9-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"peculiar","ans":[{"value":"unusual and strange, sometimes in an unpleasant way","isTrue":true},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"able to be understood:","isTrue":false},{"value":"As person who doesn't believe in god.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["She has the most peculiar ideas.","What a peculiar smell!","She got a peculiar feeling when the phone rang.","She had a peculiar expression on her face."]},{"id":"bbbbd7fa-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"deceased","ans":[{"value":"to ignore (someone) in a deliberate and insulting way","isTrue":false},{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false},{"value":"no longer living; A person who has recently died, days or years","isTrue":true},{"value":"to turn the pages of (a book, magazine, etc.) quickly","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Both his parents are deceased.","A relative of the deceased"],"info":"<b>Usage:</b><p>Dead and deceased both mean “no longer living,” but deceased is a gentler term, and people often use it when the person who died was close to them or when they are talking to someone who knew the person who died.</p>"},{"id":"bbbbd7fb-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"obfuscate","ans":[{"value":"careful and avoiding risks:","isTrue":false},{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false},{"value":"not truly honest or sincere : giving the false appearance of being honest or sincere","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make something less clear and harder to understand, especially intentionally","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He slogged away at the paperwork all day.","I've been slogging away for days on this essay and I'm still not finished."]},{"id":"bbbc4d20-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Slog","ans":[{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":false},{"value":"individually separate and distinct.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to keep doing something even though it is difficult or boring","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He slogged away at the paperwork all day.","I've been slogging away for days on this essay and I'm still not finished."]},{"id":"bbbc4d21-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"evict","ans":[{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":true},{"value":"a short line with many curves : a short, wavy line.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He was evicted from the bar for drunken and disorderly behavior","Tenants who fall behind in their rent risk being evicted."]},{"id":"bbbc4d22-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"ado","ans":[{"value":"to turn the pages of (a book, magazine, etc.) quickly","isTrue":false},{"value":"to lie or sit close together in a comfortable position","isTrue":false},{"value":"extremely silly or with no real meaning or importance","isTrue":false},{"value":"without wasting more time;","isTrue":true}],"examples":["And so, without further ado, let me introduce tonight's speaker"]},{"id":"bbbc4d23-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"implore","ans":[{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make a very serious or emotional request to (someone);to ask or beg for (something) in a very serious or emotional way","isTrue":true},{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"extremely silly or with no real meaning or importance","isTrue":false}],"examples":["She implored her son not to go.","He implored her to think of the children."]},{"id":"bbbc4d24-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"comprehend","ans":[{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":false},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":true},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He is able to fully comprehend what is happening and react appropriately.","When you strive to comprehend your code, you create better work and become better at what you do"]},{"id":"bbbc4d25-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"exploitation","ans":[{"value":"the suffering and death of a martyr.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":false},{"value":"the act of using someone unfairly for your own advantage","isTrue":true},{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Exploitation of colonies leaves them at a disadvantage and makes the colonizing nations more wealthy and powerful."]},{"id":"bbbc4d26-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"metaphor","ans":[{"value":"An expression, often found in literature, that describes a person or object by referring to something that is considered to have similar characteristics to that person or object","isTrue":true},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":false},{"value":"trying to appear or sound more important or clever than you are, especially in matters of art and literature","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The mind is an ocean.","the city is a jungle."]},{"id":"bbbc4d27-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"preemptive","ans":[{"value":"done before someone else can do it","isTrue":true},{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person, thing, or fact that is very different from other people, things, or facts, so that it cannot be used to draw general conclusions","isTrue":false},{"value":"different from what you would expect : not agreeing with what seems right or natural","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Just as Martha was about to take the only cookie left on the table, Noah preemptively swiped it."]},{"id":"bbbc4d28-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"taxing","ans":[{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":true},{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false},{"value":"seeming impossible or difficult to understand because of containing two opposite facts or characteristics","isTrue":false},{"value":"Literally meaning a lack of claim to knowledge. Generally is referring to a lack of claim to knowledge about the possible existence of god(s). But can be used for anything in general.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The hike to the summit of Mt. Whitney was so taxing that I could barely speak or stand up."]},{"id":"bbbc4d29-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"disingenuous","ans":[{"value":"not truly honest or sincere : giving the false appearance of being honest or sincere","isTrue":true},{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":false}],"examples":["That advertisement is demeaning to women.","Her statement demeans the hard work the group has done."]},{"id":"bbbc4d2a-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"demeaning","ans":[{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":true},{"value":"seeming impossible or difficult to understand because of containing two opposite facts or characteristics","isTrue":false},{"value":"the way in which you express your feelings, thoughts and ideas, etc., in words","isTrue":false}],"examples":["That advertisement is demeaning to women.","Her statement demeans the hard work the group has done."]},{"id":"bbbc4d2b-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"caveat","ans":[{"value":"a strong feeling of dislike or hatred","isTrue":false},{"value":"a comparison of two things based on their being alike in some way","isTrue":false},{"value":"an warning that should be remembered when you are doing or thinking about something","isTrue":true},{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["His investment advice comes with a caveat: that the stock market is impossible to predict with absolute accuracy."]},{"id":"bbbc4d2c-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Nuance","ans":[{"value":"to cause an angry, harmful, or violent action or feeling","isTrue":false},{"value":"Literally meaning a lack of claim to knowledge. Generally is referring to a lack of claim to knowledge about the possible existence of god(s). But can be used for anything in general.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a very slight difference in appearance, meaning, sound, etc.","isTrue":true},{"value":"seeming impossible or difficult to understand because of containing two opposite facts or characteristics","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Actors have to study the nuances of facial expression to show the whole range of emotions."]},{"id":"bbbc4d2d-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Rhetorical","ans":[{"value":"the advocacy of women's rights on the ground of the equality of the sexes.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to want to be able to move away from something because you fear it","isTrue":false},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":true},{"value":"not communicating with anyone else because you do not want to or are not allowed to:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["\"Should we be leaving soon?” “Is that a rhetorical question?” [=is that a question you're asking as a way to say that we should be leaving soon?]","My question was rhetorical. I wasn't really expecting an answer."]},{"id":"bbbc4d2e-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Sparse","ans":[{"value":"thinly dispersed or scattered.","isTrue":true},{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false},{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":false},{"value":"an area of interest or activity","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Areas of sparse population"]},{"id":"bbbc4d2f-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Emphatic","ans":[{"value":"the advocacy of women's rights on the ground of the equality of the sexes.","isTrue":false},{"value":"said or done in a forceful or definite way; resounding","isTrue":true},{"value":"an area of interest or activity","isTrue":false},{"value":"a short line with many curves : a short, wavy line.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Her answer was an emphatic “Yes!”","It was a emphatic victory."]},{"id":"bbbc4d30-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Flimsy","ans":[{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":false},{"value":"easily broken, torn, etc. : not strong or solid","isTrue":true},{"value":"very little and not enough:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["They made a flimsy argument against me.","flimsy construction."]},{"id":"bbbc4d31-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Vague","ans":[{"value":"As person who doesn't believe in god.","isTrue":false},{"value":"done before someone else can do it","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":false},{"value":"not clear in meaning; not thinking or expressing your thoughts clearly or precisely;","isTrue":true}],"examples":["Millennial is an identity given to a broadly and vaguely defined group of people.","The instructions she left were vague and difficult to follow.","He gave only a vague answer.","The judges determined that the law was too vague to be fairly enforced.","When I asked him what they talked about, he was rather vague."]},{"id":"bbbc4d32-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"squiggly","ans":[{"value":"not truly honest or sincere : giving the false appearance of being honest or sincere","isTrue":false},{"value":"a short line with many curves : a short, wavy line.","isTrue":true},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":false}],"examples":["His handwriting looks like a bunch of squiggles."]},{"id":"bbbc4d33-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"agnostic","ans":[{"value":"the suffering and death of a martyr.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a quality that makes one person or thing different from another","isTrue":false},{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":false},{"value":"Literally meaning a lack of claim to knowledge. Generally is referring to a lack of claim to knowledge about the possible existence of god(s). But can be used for anything in general.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["With layer of separation, one layer could be agnostic of other.","Few are atheists or agnostics."]},{"id":"bbbc4d34-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"analogy","ans":[{"value":"very little and not enough:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make a very serious or emotional request to (someone);to ask or beg for (something) in a very serious or emotional way","isTrue":false},{"value":"to turn the pages of (a book, magazine, etc.) quickly","isTrue":false},{"value":"a comparison of two things based on their being alike in some way","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He drew/made an analogy between flying a kite and fishing."]},{"id":"bbbc4d35-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"take a stab at (something)","ans":[{"value":"To attempt (to do) something","isTrue":true},{"value":"causing a feeling of great surprise or wonder : causing astonishment","isTrue":false},{"value":"able to be understood:","isTrue":false},{"value":"easily broken, torn, etc. : not strong or solid","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Sure, I'll take a stab at it."],"code":"derived from idiom \"stab in the dark\", meaning an attempt at something with little guidance or hope of success"},{"id":"bbbc4d36-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"thumb through","ans":[{"value":"to turn the pages of (a book, magazine, etc.) quickly","isTrue":true},{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false},{"value":"angry and bitter (typically of speech or discussion)","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make (someone) do something by using force or threats","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I thumbed through a magazine while I waited."]},{"id":"bbbc4d37-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Feminism or Feminist","ans":[{"value":"the advocacy of women's rights on the ground of the equality of the sexes.","isTrue":true},{"value":"not aware of or not noticing something, esp. what is happening around you","isTrue":false},{"value":"said or done in a forceful or definite way; resounding","isTrue":false},{"value":"different from what you would expect : not agreeing with what seems right or natural","isTrue":false}],"examples":["the feminist movement"]},{"id":"bbbc4d38-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"snub","ans":[{"value":"to ignore (someone) in a deliberate and insulting way","isTrue":true},{"value":"individually separate and distinct.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to support, strengthen, or defend (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":false}],"examples":["She snubbed me in the hallway."]},{"id":"bbbc4d39-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"extrapolate","ans":[{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to form an opinion or to make an estimate about something from known facts","isTrue":true},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to agree with someone or something","isTrue":false}],"examples":["We can extrapolate the number of new students entering next year by looking at how many entered in previous years.","With such a small study it is impossible to extrapolate accurately."]},{"id":"bbbc4d3a-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"transit","ans":[{"value":"a company that owns several smaller businesses whose products or services are usually very different:","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing someone to become or feel less respected:","isTrue":false},{"value":"very little and not enough:","isTrue":false},{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["With transit visa, you can pass by country."]},{"id":"bbbc4d3b-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"incite","ans":[{"value":"to cause an angry, harmful, or violent action or feeling","isTrue":true},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to turn the pages of (a book, magazine, etc.) quickly","isTrue":false},{"value":"a loud noise made by people who are angry or annoyed; a lot of angry comments made in public about someone or something:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The victim had done nothing to incite [=provoke] the attackers.","They were clearly trying to incite the crowd to violence."]},{"id":"bbbc7430-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"astonishing","ans":[{"value":"a loud noise made by people who are angry or annoyed; a lot of angry comments made in public about someone or something:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing a feeling of great surprise or wonder : causing astonishment","isTrue":true},{"value":"to make (someone) do something by using force or threats","isTrue":false}],"examples":["She gave an astonishing performance in her first film.","an astonishingly beautiful scene"]},{"id":"bbbc7431-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"concur","ans":[{"value":"to agree with someone or something","isTrue":true},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make something less effective : to ruin or spoil (something)","isTrue":false},{"value":"to know or guess about something before it happens:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["We concur that more money should be spent on education.","She concurred with the judge."]},{"id":"bbbc7432-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"animosity","ans":[{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":false},{"value":"the action of passing through or across a place.; the carrying of people or things from one place to another.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a strong feeling of dislike or hatred","isTrue":true},{"value":"a person with whom one shares a secret or private matter, trusting them not to repeat it to others.","isTrue":false}],"examples":["There has always been animosity between India and Pakistan."]},{"id":"bbbc7433-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"chaperone","ans":[{"value":"very harsh and critical","isTrue":false},{"value":"very strongly felt; very great; absolute or complete","isTrue":false},{"value":"someone (such as a teacher or parent) who goes with children on a trip or to a school dance to make sure that the children behave properly","isTrue":true},{"value":"not truly honest or sincere : giving the false appearance of being honest or sincere","isTrue":false}],"examples":["I was a chaperone on one of my son's school trips."]},{"id":"bbbc7434-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"traits","ans":[{"value":"having too much interest in and admiration for yourself:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to be a very good example of (something) : to show (something) very clearly","isTrue":false},{"value":"a quality that makes one person or thing different from another","isTrue":true},{"value":"a strange or unusual habit, way of behaving, or feature that someone or something has:","isTrue":false}],"examples":["Humility is an admirable trait."]},{"id":"bbbc7435-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"martyrdom","ans":[{"value":"said in a clear and short way; expressing what needs to be said without unnecessary words","isTrue":false},{"value":"the suffering and death of a martyr.","isTrue":true},{"value":"someone (such as a teacher or parent) who goes with children on a trip or to a school dance to make sure that the children behave properly","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make a very serious or emotional request to (someone);to ask or beg for (something) in a very serious or emotional way","isTrue":false}],"examples":["He suffered martyrdom for his religious beliefs."]},{"id":"bbbc7436-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"martyr","ans":[{"value":"to keep doing something even though it is difficult or boring","isTrue":false},{"value":"use to the limit; exhaust","isTrue":false},{"value":"thinly dispersed or scattered.","isTrue":false},{"value":"a person who is killed or who suffers greatly for a religion, cause, etc.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["They know that killing him will only make a martyr out of him."]},{"id":"bbbc7437-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"semantics","ans":[{"value":"the act of using someone unfairly for your own advantage","isTrue":false},{"value":"to force someone to leave somewhere","isTrue":false},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the meaning and interpretation of words, signs and sentence structure.","isTrue":true}],"examples":["The whole controversy is a matter of semantics."]},{"id":"bbbc7438-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"guzzle","ans":[{"value":"An expression, often found in literature, that describes a person or object by referring to something that is considered to have similar characteristics to that person or object","isTrue":false},{"value":"the way in which you express your feelings, thoughts and ideas, etc., in words","isTrue":false},{"value":"Something that is given to a person in return for something they have done, often use in a bad sense.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to drink quickly, eagerly, and usually in large amounts","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He guzzled his beer and ordered another.","Telecom business is a money guzzler."]},{"id":"bbbc7439-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"snuggle","ans":[{"value":"to keep doing something even though it is difficult or boring","isTrue":false},{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":false},{"value":"to ignore (someone) in a deliberate and insulting way","isTrue":false},{"value":"to lie or sit close together in a comfortable position","isTrue":true}],"examples":["The puppy snuggled up against the sleeping boy.","The boy snuggled close to his mother."]},{"id":"bbbc743a-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"hysteria","ans":[{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":false},{"value":"the act of using someone unfairly for your own advantage","isTrue":false},{"value":"a situation in which many people behave or react in an extreme or uncontrolled way because of fear, anger, etc.","isTrue":true},{"value":"extremely silly or with no real meaning or importance","isTrue":false}],"examples":["People were in hysteria after the death of their beloved actor.","A few of the children began to scream, and soon they were all caught up in the hysteria."]},{"id":"bbbc743b-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"profound","ans":[{"value":"the state of having a lot of money and possessions","isTrue":false},{"value":"to understand something completely, often bit difficult.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to form an opinion or to make an estimate about something from known facts","isTrue":false},{"value":"very strongly felt; very great; absolute or complete","isTrue":true}],"examples":["I profoundly apologize.","a profound silence.","a profound thinker."]},{"id":"bbbc743c-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"coerce","ans":[{"value":"to be slow or late about doing something that should be done; to delay doing something until a later time because you do not want to do it, because you are lazy, etc.","isTrue":false},{"value":"not clear in meaning; not thinking or expressing your thoughts clearly or precisely;","isTrue":false},{"value":"to name things separately, one by one:","isTrue":false},{"value":"to make (someone) do something by using force or threats","isTrue":true}],"examples":["He was coerced into signing the confession.","Soldiers coerced the residents into giving them food.","The singer was coerced into a contract with the record company."]},{"id":"bbbc743d-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Atheist","ans":[{"value":"As person who doesn't believe in god.","isTrue":true},{"value":"A question : asked in order to make a statement rather than to get an answer.","isTrue":false},{"value":"the act of using someone unfairly for your own advantage","isTrue":false},{"value":"trying to appear or sound more important or clever than you are, especially in matters of art and literature","isTrue":false}]},{"id":"bbbc743e-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Caustic","ans":[{"value":"trying to appear or sound more important or clever than you are, especially in matters of art and literature","isTrue":false},{"value":"a loud noise made by people who are angry or annoyed; a lot of angry comments made in public about someone or something:","isTrue":false},{"value":"despite the stated thing; although:","isTrue":false},{"value":"very harsh and critical","isTrue":true}],"examples":["caustic film reviews","She wrote a caustic report about the decisions that led to the crisis.","caustic humor/wit"]},{"id":"bbbc743f-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"despair","ans":[{"value":"to agree or have the same opinion","isTrue":false},{"value":"causing a feeling of great surprise or wonder : causing astonishment","isTrue":false},{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":true},{"value":"personal confidence or courage that allows someone to do or say things that may seem shocking to others","isTrue":false}],"examples":["His despair nearly drove him mad.","She let out a cry of despair. [=desperation]","I was overcome by despair at being unable to find them."]},{"id":"bbbc7440-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Buttress","ans":[{"value":"the feeling of no longer having any hope","isTrue":false},{"value":"to support, strengthen, or defend (something)","isTrue":true},{"value":"a temporary prohibition of an activity.;a delay or suspension of an activity or a law","isTrue":false},{"value":"a comparison of two things based on their being alike in some way","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The treaty will buttress the cause of peace.","The theory has been buttressed by the results of the experiment."]},{"id":"bbbc7441-b645-11ea-b30f-d9405d426e1a","question":"Ramparts","ans":[{"value":"a tall, thick stone or dirt wall that is built around a castle, town, etc., to protect it from attacks","isTrue":true},{"value":"a quality that makes one person or thing different from another","isTrue":false},{"value":"the advocacy of women's rights on the ground of the equality of the sexes.","isTrue":false},{"value":"to support, strengthen, or defend (something)","isTrue":false}],"examples":["The city's ramparts crumbled long ago."]}]